{"showBridgeTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40181/":{"taskOID":40181,"originalTaskOID":40181,"setID":490,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5081,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Cleaning","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of cleaning do you need? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2775,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Requires cleaning/maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Requires cleaning/maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6006,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stain removal","answerDisplayText":"Stain removal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4662,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Pet stains","answerDisplayText":"Pet stains","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2120,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Dust","answerDisplayText":"Dust","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1937,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Dirt/grime","answerDisplayText":"Dirt/grime","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3843,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Mildew","answerDisplayText":"Mildew","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5083,"questionDisplayText":"Repairs Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you need any repairs? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1641,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Cords","answerDisplayText":"Cords","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2924,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Hardware tightened/adjusted","answerDisplayText":"Hardware tightened/adjusted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4137,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"New clips","answerDisplayText":"New clips","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2916,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Handles/controls replaced","answerDisplayText":"Handles/controls replaced","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5081,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Cleaning","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of cleaning do you need? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2775,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Requires cleaning/maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Requires cleaning/maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6006,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stain removal","answerDisplayText":"Stain removal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4662,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Pet stains","answerDisplayText":"Pet stains","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2120,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Dust","answerDisplayText":"Dust","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1937,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Dirt/grime","answerDisplayText":"Dirt/grime","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3843,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Mildew","answerDisplayText":"Mildew","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2775,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Requires cleaning/maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Requires cleaning/maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6006,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stain removal","answerDisplayText":"Stain removal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4662,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Pet stains","answerDisplayText":"Pet stains","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2120,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Dust","answerDisplayText":"Dust","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1937,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Dirt/grime","answerDisplayText":"Dirt/grime","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3843,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Mildew","answerDisplayText":"Mildew","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5083,"questionDisplayText":"Repairs Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you need any repairs? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1641,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Cords","answerDisplayText":"Cords","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2924,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Hardware tightened/adjusted","answerDisplayText":"Hardware tightened/adjusted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4137,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"New clips","answerDisplayText":"New clips","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2916,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Handles/controls replaced","answerDisplayText":"Handles/controls replaced","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1641,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Cords","answerDisplayText":"Cords","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2924,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Hardware tightened/adjusted","answerDisplayText":"Hardware tightened/adjusted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4137,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"New clips","answerDisplayText":"New clips","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2916,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Handles/controls replaced","answerDisplayText":"Handles/controls replaced","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"taskHeader":"Curtain Cleaning Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40181/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40181,"taskName":"Drapes or Curtains - Clean","taskDescription":"Clean or Treat Drapes or Curtains","xmTaskDescriptor":"Curtain Cleaning Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":274,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Drapes Curtains carpet cleaning moisture","textMessagingName":"Clean Drapes","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes both the cleaning of drapes \u0026 curtains in the home or office. Also the onsite taking down of the drapes \u0026 taking them elsewhere to be cleaned, bringing them back \u0026 reinstalling them. May include application of fabric protection sprays.","rolloverShortDesc":"Cleaned in home or taken to plant.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local curtain cleaning services. HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated drape and curtain cleaners in your area","htmlTitle":"Curtain Cleaning \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Clean Drapes \u0026 Curtains","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":10,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Clean Drapes or Curtains","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Drapes or Curtains - Clean","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Drapes and Curtain Cleaning Project","urlName":"Drapes-or-Curtains-Clean","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Curtain Cleaning Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Costs, Reviews","searchKeywords":"Drapes,Curtains,carpet,cleaning,moisture,low,cleaners,berber,fabric,cleaner,Clean","emcCategoryOid":-12011,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":490,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}